Guide to the Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 3. Personal, Political and Official Files, 1944-2010 TJU.2010.01.03
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Political Party Involvement, 1978-2006; IV.
  - Abortion issues, 1995 (Box 514, Folder 5)
  - Abortion platform, undated (Box 514, Folder 6)
  - Acari Indexes, 1981-1985 (Box 514, Folder 7)
  - Accomplishments and four-year reports, 1983-1989 (Box 514, Folder 8)
  - Accomplishments letters, 1988-1990 (Box 514, Folder 9)
  - Accomplishments letters, 100th Congress, 1988 (Box 514, Folder 10)
  - Accomplishments letters, 101st Congress, 1989 (Box 514, Folder 11)
  - Accomplishments letters, 101st Congress, 1990 (Box 514, Folder 12-13)
  - Accomplishments letters, 101st Congress, 1990-1991 (Box 514, Folder 14)
  - Activity records, 1986 (Box 514, Folder 15)
  - Administrative memos, 1983-1984 (Box 514, Folder 16)
  - African-American Chamber of Commerce questionnaire, 2004 (Box 514, Folder 17)
  - Lamar Alexander, 1994-1996 (Box 514, Folder 18)
  - Allegheny County Medical Society questionnaire, 2004 (Box 514, Folder 19)
  - Alliance for Retired Americans questionnaire, 2004 (Box 514, Folder 20)
  - American Association of Retired Persons (AARP) questionnaire, 2004 (Box 514, Folder 21)
  - American Conservative Union Congressional ratings, 1981-1985 (Box 514, Folder 22)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Oraganizations (AFL-CIO) questionnaire, 2004 (Box 514, Folder 23)
  - AFL-CIO report on Congress, 2001 (Box 514, Folder 24)
  - Appropriations bill issues, 1984-1985 (Box 514, Folder 25)
  - Ballot Access News, 1995 (Box 514, Folder 26)
  - William Bennett, 1994-1995 (Box 514, Folder 27)
  - Big Tent, Committee correspondence, 1994 (Box 514, Folder 28)
  - Big Tent, Federal Election Commission reports, 1993-1994 (Box 514, Folder 29)
  - Big Tent, Income summaries, 1994 (Box 514, Folder 30)
  - Big Tent, Lease, 1994 (Box 514, Folder 31)
  - Big Tent, Lunches and solicitation, 1994 (Box 514, Folder 32)
  - Big Tent, Memos, 1993-1994 (Box 514, Folder 33)
  - Big Tent, Newsclips, 1994 (Box 514, Folder 34)
  - Big Tent, Notes, 1994 (Box 514, Folder 35)
  - Big Tent, Political Action Committee (PAC), 1992-1994 (Box 514, Folder 36)
  - Big Tent, PAC, 1994-1995 (Box 515, Folder 1)
  - Big Tent, Polling material, 1994 (Box 515, Folder 2)
  - Big Tent, Reimbursements, 1994 (Box 515, Folder 3)
  - Big Tent, Speeches, 1994 (Box 515, Folder 4)
  - Big Tent, Values, 1994 (Box 515, Folder 5)
  - Big Tent, Washington Republican meetings, 1994 (Box 515, Folder 6)
  - Bills co-sponsored by Specter, 1993-1994 (Box 515, Folder 7)
  - Hiram Bingham, 2000-2002 (Box 515, Folder 8)
  - Binney & Smith visit, 1986 (Box 515, Folder 9)
  - Black Senate Legislative Caucus, 1983-1988 (Box 515, Folder 10)
  - Michael Blume, Research on economic development, 1990 (Box 515, Folder 11-12)
  - Bosnia-related voting records, 1994-1995 (Box 515, Folder 13)
  - Briefing book, Formosa, 2002 (Box 515, Folder 14)
  - Briefing book, Introduction, 2002 (Box 515, Folder 15)
  - Briefing book, Korean War, 2002 (Box 515, Folder 16)
  - Briefing book, Lebanon, 2002 (Box 515, Folder 17)
  - Briefing book, Middle East, 2002 (Box 515, Folder 18)
  - Briefing book, Miscellaneous information, 2002 (Box 515, Folder 19)
  - Briefing book, Notable debates, Bosnia and Iraq, 2002 (Box 515, Folder 20)
  - Briefing book, Persian Gulf, 2002 (Box 515, Folder 21)
  - Briefing book, Terrorist attacks, 2002 (Box 515, Folder 22)
  - Briefing book, Unauthorized use of military abroad, 2002 (Box 515, Folder 23)
  - Briefing book, Vietnam War, 2002 (Box 515, Folder 24)
  - Briefing book, World War I, 2002 (Box 515, Folder 25)
  - Briefing book, World War II, 2002 (Box 515, Folder 26)
  - Pat Buchanan, 1994-1995 (Box 515, Folder 27)
  - Budget information, 1985 (Box 515, Folder 28)
  - Building trades votes, 1981-1985 (Box 515, Folder 29)
  - Business-Industry PAC action reports, 1982-1984 (Box 515, Folder 30)
  - Citizens against Government Waste Senate rankings, 2001 (Box 515, Folder 31)
  - Citizens for Arlen Specter (CAS), 1983-1984 (Box 515, Folder 32)
  - CAS, 1985-1990 (Box 515, Folder 33)
  - CAS, 1991-1992 (Box 515, Folder 34)
  - CAS, Car, 1990-1993 (Box 515, Folder 35)
  - CAS Day, 1983 (Box 515, Folder 36)
  - CAS Day, 1984 (Box 515, Folder 37)
  - CAS Day, 1988 (Box 515, Folder 38)
  - CAS Day, 1991 (Box 515, Folder 39)
  - CAS Day, 1992 (Box 515, Folder 40)
  - CAS Day, 1993-1994 (Box 515, Folder 41)
  - CAS, Event schedules, 1997 (Box 515, Folder 42)
  - CAS, Fundraising, 1989 (Box 515, Folder 43)
  - CAS, Fundraising, 1990 (Box 515, Folder 44)
  - CAS, Invitations, 1985 (Box 515, Folder 45)
  - CAS, Members, 1983-1985 (Box 515, Folder 46)
  - CAS, Members by county, 1985 (Box 515, Folder 47)
  - CAS, Members by county, undated (Box 515, Folder 48)
  - CAS, Phone logs, 1983 (Box 516, Folder 1)
  - CAS, Steering Committee, 1984 (Box 516, Folder 2)
  - Citizens Committee for the Right to Keep and Bear Arms, 1994 (Box 516, Folder 3)
  - Clean Water Action questionnaire, 2004 (Box 516, Folder 4)
  - Clinton/Gore campaign stances, 1992 (Box 516, Folder 5)
  - Coal Caucus, 1985-1989 (Box 516, Folder 6)
  - Coalition for Peace Action questionnaire, 2004 (Box 516, Folder 7)
  - Coin bill information, 1992 (Box 516, Folder 8)
  - Colorado Republicans Presidential Forum Dinner, 1995 (Box 516, Folder 9)
  - Commission on Civil Rights, 1982 (Box 516, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Committees, 1986 (Box 516, Folder 11)
  - Committee for Honest Elections, Hoboken, 1985 (Box 516, Folder 12)
  - Committee for Honest Elections, Philadelphia, 1985-1986 (Box 516, Folder 13)
  - Common cause, 1988-1989 (Box 516, Folder 14)
  - Congratulatory correspondence, 1982 (Box 516, Folder 15)
  - Congratulatory correspondence, 1987 (Box 516, Folder 16)
  - Congratulatory correspondence, 1994 (Box 516, Folder 17)
  - Congressional arrests, 1988 (Box 516, Folder 18)
  - Congressional Quarterly, 1981-2003 (Box 516, Folder 19)
  - Congressional Quarterly, Politics in America, 1991 (Box 516, Folder 20)
  - Congressional Quarterly ratings, 1986 (Box 516, Folder 21)
  - Congressional votes on abortion, 1981-1982 (Box 516, Folder 22)
  - Conservative Caucus Foundation Senate report, 1980-1985 (Box 516, Folder 23)
  - Contribution requests, 1980-1981 (Box 516, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence regarding meetings, 1994 (Box 516, Folder 25)
  - County issues, 1990-1992 (Box 516, Folder 26)
  - County profile, Adams County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 27)
  - County profile, Allegheny County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 28)
  - County profile, Armstrong County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 29)
  - County profile, Beaver County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 30)
  - County profile, Bedford County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 31)
  - County profile, Berks County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 32)
  - County profile, Blair County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 33)
  - County profile, Bradford County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 34)
  - County profile, Bucks County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 35)
  - County profile, Butler County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 36)
  - County profile, Cambria County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 37)
  - County profile, Cameron County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 38)
  - County profile, Carbon County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 39)
  - County profile, Centre County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 40)
  - County profile, Chester County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 41)
  - County profile, Clarion County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 42)
  - County profile, Clearfield County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 43)
  - County profile, Clinton County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 44)
  - County profile, Columbia County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 45)
  - County profile, Crawford County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 46)
  - County profile, Cumberland County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 47)
  - County profile, Dauphin County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 48)
  - County profile, Delaware County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 49)
  - County profile, Elk County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 50)
  - County profile, Erie County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 51)
  - County profile, Fayette County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 52)
  - County profile, Forest County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 53)
  - County profile, Franklin County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 54)
  - County profile, Fulton County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 55)
  - County profile, Greene County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 56)
  - County profile, Huntingdon County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 57)
  - County profile, Indiana County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 58)
  - County profile, Jefferson County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 59)
  - County profile, Juniata County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 60)
  - County profile, Lackawanna County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 61)
  - County profile, Lancaster County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 62)
  - County profile, Lawrence County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 63)
  - County profile, Lebanon County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 64)
  - County profile, Lehigh County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 65)
  - County profile, Lycoming County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 66)
  - County profile, McKean County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 67)
  - County profile, Mercer County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 68)
  - County profile, Mifflin County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 69)
  - County profile, Monroe County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 70)
  - County profile, Montgomery County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 71)
  - County profile, Montour County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 72)
  - County profile, Northampton County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 73)
  - County profile, Northumberland County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 74)
  - County profile, Perry County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 75)
  - County profile, Philadelphia County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 76)
  - County profile, Pike County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 77)
  - County profile, Potter County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 78)
  - County profile, Schuylkill County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 79)
  - County profile, Snyder County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 80)
  - County profile, Somerset County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 81)
  - County profile, Sullivan County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 82)
  - County profile, Susquehanna County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 83)
  - County profile, Tioga County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 84)
  - County profile, Union County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 85)
  - County profile, Venango County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 86)
  - County profile, Warren County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 87)
  - County profile, Washington County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 88)
  - County profile, Wayne County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 89)
  - County profile, Westmoreland County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 90)
  - County profile, Wyoming County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 91)
  - County profile, York County, 1981-1986 (Box 516, Folder 92)
  - County visits, 1996 (Box 516, Folder 93)
  - Crime legislation introduced by Specter, 1981-1994 (Box 516, Folder 94)
  - Crime stances, 1984 (Box 516, Folder 95)
  - Defense Base Closure and Realignment Commission, 1995 (Box 516, Folder 96)
  - Democratic Senatorial Campaign Committee, Women's Council, undated (Box 516, Folder 97)
  - District of Columbia appropriation bills, 1984-1994 (Box 516, Folder 98)
  - Bob Dole, 1995-1996 (Box 516, Folder 99)
  - Robin Chandler Duke, 1999-2000 (Box 516, Folder 100)
  - Election letters, 2006 (Box 517, Folder 1)
  - Energy organizations, 1984-1985 (Box 517, Folder 2)
  - Event invitations, 1983-1985 (Box 517, Folder 3)
  - Event invitations, 1986 (Box 517, Folder 4-5)
  - Event invitations, 1987 (Box 517, Folder 6-8)
  - Fight Crime; Invest in Kids questionnaire, 2004 (Box 517, Folder 9)
  - Freedom Republicans, 1984-1996 (Box 517, Folder 10)
  - Freedom Republicans, 1985-1991 (Box 517, Folder 11)
  - Stephen Freind, 1992 (Box 517, Folder 12)
  - Friends Committee on National Legislation, Washington newsletter, 1981-1997 (Box 517, Folder 13)
  - Friends of the Earth ratings on energy policy, 1982 (Box 517, Folder 14)
  - Fundraising event planning, 1991 (Box 517, Folder 15)
  - Fundraising for other campaigns, 1981 (Box 517, Folder 16)
  - Geoff Gibbs, 1994 (Box 517, Folder 17)
  - Phil Gramm, 1995 (Box 517, Folder 18)
  - GOP National Convention, 2000 (Box 517, Folder 19)
  - GOP National Convention requests, 2000 (Box 517, Folder 20)
  - Health care reform, 1992 (Box 517, Folder 21)
  - House of Representatives votes on energy and the environment, 1983 (Box 517, Folder 22)
  - How They Voted, U.S. Chamber of Commerce, 2001 (Box 517, Folder 23)
  - Human Events Congress ratings, 1979-1984 (Box 517, Folder 24)
  - Inauguration ceremonies, 1988-1989 (Box 517, Folder 25)
  - Inaugural requests, 1988-1989 (Box 517, Folder 26)
  - Issue papers, 1990-1992 (Box 517, Folder 27)
  - Issue papers, 1994 (Box 517, Folder 28)
  - Jewish impact on politics, 1988 (Box 517, Folder 29)
  - Jewish mailing lists, 1987-1988 (Box 517, Folder 30)
  - Judiciary Committee legislation, 1995-1997 (Box 517, Folder 31)
  - Juvenile Justice Subcommittee talking points and legislation, 1981-1984 (Box 518, Folder 1)
  - Labor endorsements, 1990-1992 (Box 518, Folder 2)
  - League of Women Voters of Pennsylvania questionnaire, 2004 (Box 518, Folder 3)
  - League of Women Voters of Pennsylvania, Venango campus debate, 1986 (Box 518, Folder 4)
  - Legislation introduced by Specter, 1992-1994 (Box 518, Folder 5)
  - Legislative accomplishments, 1991 (Box 518, Folder 6)
  - Legislative profile reports, 1989-1994 (Box 518, Folder 7)
  - Letters to donors, 1981 (Box 518, Folder 8)
  - Richard Lugar, 1995 (Box 518, Folder 9)
  - Machinists votes, 1996-1998 (Box 518, Folder 10)
  - Main Line Chamber of Commerce questionnaire, 2004 (Box 518, Folder 11)
  - Market Opinion Research, Focus groups on Specter, 1984-1985 (Box 518, Folder 12)
  - Medicare Rights Center questionnaire, 2004 (Box 518, Folder 13)
  - Memos on senior citizens legislation, 1996 (Box 518, Folder 14)
  - Mubarak visit to Washington, 1989 (Box 518, Folder 15)
  - Edmund Muskie, 1998 (Box 518, Folder 16)
  - National Abortion Rights Action League (NARAL) questionnaire, 2004 (Box 518, Folder 17)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1984 (Box 518, Folder 18)
  - National Audio-Visual Association, 1985 (Box 518, Folder 19)
  - National Education Association questionnaire, 2004 (Box 518, Folder 20)
  - November elections, 1991 (Box 518, Folder 21)
  - Michael O'Rourke, 1980-1983 (Box 518, Folder 22)
  - Ocean County Jewish Federation dinner, 1983 (Box 518, Folder 23)
  - Office memos, 1985-1986 (Box 518, Folder 24)
  - Party of Lincoln, 1992 (Box 518, Folder 25)
  - Pennsylvania Association for Adult Continuing Education questionnaire, 2004 (Box 518, Folder 26)
  - Pennsylvania Association of Staff Nurses and Allied Professionals questionnaire, 2004 (Box 518, Folder 27)
  - Pennsylvania Bankers Association questionnaire, 2004 (Box 518, Folder 28)
  - Pennsylvania Family Institute questionnaire, 2004 (Box 518, Folder 29)
  - Pennsylvania Gay and Lesbian Alliance questionnaire, 2004 (Box 518, Folder 30)
  - Pennsylvania Gazette feature, 1984 (Box 518, Folder 31)
  - Pennsylvania Homecare Association questionnaire, 2004 (Box 518, Folder 32)
  - Pennsylvania Hunger Action Center questionnaire, 2004 (Box 518, Folder 33)
  - Pennsylvania organizations, undated (Box 518, Folder 34)
  - Pennsylvania publications, 1985 (Box 518, Folder 35)
  - Pennsylvania State Committee members, 1984 (Box 518, Folder 36)
  - The People, the Press & Politics: The New Political Landscape, 1994 (Box 518, Folder 37)
  - Personal attendance report, 1995-1996 (Box 518, Folder 38)
  - Philadelphia visits, 1982-1984 (Box 518, Folder 39)
  - Pittsburgh Metro Area Postal Workers Union questionnaire, 2004 (Box 518, Folder 40)
  - Pizza dinners, 1983-1984 (Box 518, Folder 41)
  - Planned Parenthood questionnaire, 2004 (Box 518, Folder 42)
  - Political newsclips, 1983-1984 (Box 518, Folder 43)
  - Politically Active Physicians Association Conference, 2003 (Box 518, Folder 44)
  - Poll on opinions of Specter, undated (Box 518, Folder 45)
  - Position, Abortion, 1992-1995 (Box 518, Folder 46-47)
  - Position, Abortion, 1995-1996 (Box 518, Folder 48-49)
  - Position, Product liability, 1996 (Box 518, Folder 50)
  - Colin Powell, 1994-1995 (Box 518, Folder 51)
  - Presiding Officer hours, 1995-2001 (Box 519, Folder 1)
  - Presiding Officers totals, 1985-1986 (Box 519, Folder 2)
  - Press and statements on health care, 1993-2003 (Box 519, Folder 3)
  - Press releases on Specter bills, 1983 (Box 519, Folder 4)
  - Product liability statements, 1995-1996 (Box 519, Folder 5)
  - Program funding work, 1984-1985 (Box 519, Folder 6)
  - Project Vote Smart questionnaire, 2004 (Box 519, Folder 7)
  - Reading Eagle questionnaire, 2004 (Box 519, Folder 8)
  - Reagan support, 1984-1985 (Box 519, Folder 9)
  - Recommendations, 1980-1981 (Box 519, Folder 10)
  - Recommendations, 1981-1982 (Box 519, Folder 11)
  - Record on key conservative issues, 2003 (Box 519, Folder 12)
  - Religious Right newsclips, 1993-1994 (Box 519, Folder 13-14)
  - Republican Majority Coalition Big Tent, California, 1993 (Box 519, Folder 15)
  - Republican Majority Coalition Big Tent, Chicago, 1992-1993 (Box 519, Folder 16)
  - Republican Majority Coalition Big Tent, Chicago, 1993 (Box 519, Folder 17)
  - Republican Majority Coalition Big Tent, Chicago, Senator's file, 1993 (Box 519, Folder 18)
  - Republican Majority Coalition Big Tent, Philadelphia, 1992-1993 (Box 519, Folder 19)
  - Republican Majority Coalition Big Tent, Phoenix, 1993 (Box 519, Folder 20)
  - Republican Majority Coalition, May hearing, 1993 (Box 519, Folder 21)
  - Republican Majority Coalition, June hearing, 1993 (Box 519, Folder 22)
  - Republican Majority Coalition, November/December hearings, 1993 (Box 519, Folder 23-24)
  - Republican Majority Coalition, Purpose, 1992-1994 (Box 519, Folder 25)
  - Republican National Committee (RNC), Iowa, 1994 (Box 519, Folder 26)
  - RNC, Iowa, 1994 (Box 520, Folder 1)
  - RNC, Minneapolis, 1994 (Box 520, Folder 2)
  - Republican polling information, Illinois, 1994-1995 (Box 520, Folder 3)
  - Republican polling information, Kansas, 1995 (Box 520, Folder 4)
  - Republican polling information, Kentucky, 1995 (Box 520, Folder 5)
  - Republican polling information, Louisiana, 1995 (Box 520, Folder 6)
  - Republican polling information, Maine, 1995 (Box 520, Folder 7)
  - Republican polling information, Maryland, 1995 (Box 520, Folder 8)
  - Republican polling information, Memos, 1995 (Box 520, Folder 9)
  - Republican polling information, Michigan, 1995 (Box 520, Folder 10)
  - Republican polling information, Minnesota, 1991-1995 (Box 520, Folder 11)
  - Republican polling information, Mississippi, 1995 (Box 520, Folder 12)
  - Republican polling information, New Jersey, 1995 (Box 520, Folder 13)
  - Republican polling information, New Mexico, 1995 (Box 520, Folder 14)
  - Republican polling information, New York, 1995 (Box 520, Folder 15)
  - Republican polling information, North Dakota, 1995 (Box 520, Folder 16)
  - Republican polling information, Ohio, 1995 (Box 520, Folder 17)
  - Republican polling information, Oregon, 1994-1995 (Box 520, Folder 18)
  - Republican polling information, Rhode Island, 1995 (Box 520, Folder 19)
  - Republican polling information, South Carolina, 1995 (Box 520, Folder 20)
  - Republican polling information, South Dakota, 1995 (Box 520, Folder 21)
  - Republican polling information, Vermont, 1993-1996 (Box 520, Folder 22)
  - Republican polling information, Virginia, 1995 (Box 520, Folder 23)
  - Republican polling information, Washington, 1995 (Box 520, Folder 24)
  - Republican polling information, Wisconsin, 1995 (Box 520, Folder 25)
  - Republican State Committee of Pennsylvania, 1994 (Box 520, Folder 26)
  - Republican State Committee of Pennsylvania letter, 1985 (Box 520, Folder 27)
  - Republican ward leaders, 1981-1982 (Box 520, Folder 28)
  - Research on Bob Edgar, 1983 (Box 520, Folder 29)
  - Responses to stance on Clinton impeachment, 1999 (Box 520, Folder 30)
  - Senate activity statistics, 1982-1991 (Box 520, Folder 31)
  - Senate floor schedules, 1984-1985 (Box 520, Folder 32)
  - Senate Majority Celebration of Character, 1999 (Box 520, Folder 33)
  - Senate vote ratings, 1984 (Box 520, Folder 34)
  - Senate vote records, 1995 (Box 520, Folder 35)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU) questionnaire, 2004 (Box 520, Folder 36)
  - Sierra Club questionnaire, 2004 (Box 520, Folder 37)
  - Specter accomplishments, 103rd Congress, 1993-1995 (Box 520, Folder 38)
  - Specter accomplishments, 104th Congress, 1995-1997 (Box 520, Folder 39)
  - Specter accomplishments, 105th Congress, 1997-1998 (Box 520, Folder 40)
  - Specter, Bills sponsored, 1981 (Box 520, Folder 41)
  - Specter candidate questionnaires, 1998 (Box 520, Folder 42)
  - Specter Congressional Quarterly votes, 1981-1984 (Box 520, Folder 43)
  - Specter correspondence, 97th Congress, 1st Session, 1981 (Box 520, Folder 44)
  - Specter correspondence, 97th Congress, 2nd Session, 1982 (Box 520, Folder 45-46)
  - Specter, Bob Dole, Stances on sex and violence in the media, 1995 (Box 521, Folder 1)
  - Specter mentions in the news, 1985-1994 (Box 521, Folder 2)
  - Specter missed votes, 1987 (Box 521, Folder 3)
  - Specter missed votes, 1988 (Box 521, Folder 4)
  - Specter missed votes, 1989 (Box 521, Folder 5)
  - Specter missed votes, 1990 (Box 521, Folder 6)
  - Specter missed votes, 1991 (Box 521, Folder 7)
  - Specter missed votes, 1992 (Box 521, Folder 8)
  - Specter missed votes, 1993 (Box 521, Folder 9)
  - Specter RNC collaboration, 1980-1982 (Box 521, Folder 10)
  - Specter Senatorial committee hearing attendance records, 1985 (Box 521, Folder 11)
  - Specter seniority, 1992 (Box 521, Folder 12)
  - Specter suggestions for Senate reforms, 1984-1989 (Box 521, Folder 13)
  - Specter vote ratings, National Journal, 1986 (Box 521, Folder 14)
  - Specter voting record, 1981 (Box 521, Folder 15)
  - Specter voting record, 1982-1983 (Box 521, Folder 16)
  - Specter voting record, 1985 (Box 521, Folder 17)
  - Specter voting record, 1986 (Box 521, Folder 18)
  - Specter voting record, 1987 (Box 521, Folder 19)
  - Specter voting record, 1987-1988 (Box 521, Folder 20)
  - Specter voting record, 1988-1989 (Box 521, Folder 21)
  - Specter voting record and attendance, 1994-1995 (Box 521, Folder 22)
  - Specter voting record, Chamber of Commerce, 1983-1984 (Box 521, Folder 23)
  - Specter voting record, Presidential support, 1985 (Box 521, Folder 24)
  - Specter voting stances, 1994-1995 (Box 521, Folder 25)
  - Specter's dealings with presidential candidates, 1987-1988 (Box 521, Folder 26)
  - Specter's labor group standings, 1985 (Box 521, Folder 27)
  - Specter's luncheon about Pennsylvania legislature, 1984 (Box 521, Folder 28)
  - Specter's positions on issues, 1994-1995 (Box 521, Folder 29-30)
  - Specter's sponsored measures and amendments, 1996 (Box 521, Folder 31)
  - State expenditures, 1979-1986 (Box 521, Folder 32)
  - State of the Union address, 1996 (Box 521, Folder 33)
  - States' stances on abortion, 1990-1994 (Box 521, Folder 34)
  - Strategic Arms Reduction Treaty, 1988 (Box 521, Folder 35)
  - Surveys sent to the state, 1983 (Box 521, Folder 36)
  - Talking points, 1983 (Box 521, Folder 37)
  - Talking points, 1984 (Box 521, Folder 38)
  - Treaty on extradition between the U.S. and Ireland, 1983 (Box 521, Folder 39)
  - Trial Lawyers Association questionnaire, 2004 (Box 521, Folder 40)
  - United Auto Workers questionnaire, 2004 (Box 521, Folder 41)
  - United Jewish Appeal, 1995 (Box 521, Folder 42)
  - United States Senate Library, 1985 (Box 521, Folder 43)
  - Veterans Association Stars and Stripes Healthcare Network, 1999 (Box 521, Folder 44)